Elizabeth Ahn Toupin Papers MS064
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Publications and Presentations, 1959 -- 2009; MS064.004.000001; 1.2 Linear Feet
  - Asian-American Friends, 1986 -- 1991; MS064.005.004.00038 (Box MS064 Shared 3)
  - Bradley Family, 1979 -- 2005; MS064.005.004.00039 (Box MS064 Shared 3)
  - Chang, Anita (Tufts Student and Filmmaker), 1994 -- 1998; MS064.005.004.00040 (Box MS064 Shared 3)
  - Chang, Edmond Yiteh, 1987 -- 1989; MS064.005.004.00041 (Box MS064 Shared 3)
  - Chin, Tsai, 1982 -- 1995; MS064.005.004.00042 (Box MS064 Shared 3)
- Personal and Family, 1935 -- 2011; MS064.005; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains personal correspondence, press releases and clippings, and photographs, as well as the unpublished memoirs of Howard Rasmussen, scientist and physician and Toupin's living companion later in life.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by last name (regardless of format of name on folder).
  - Chun, Gloria, 1986 -- 1997; MS064.005.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Clippings and Press Releases, 1969 -- 1992; MS064.005.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Jewel Cobb, 1970 -- 1974; MS064.005.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Cohen-Family, 1983 -- 2011; MS064.005.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Downing, Mike and Peter, 1994 -- 2007; MS064.005.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Ethan & Natalie Ferrier, 1993; MS064.005.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Friends [1 of 2], 1993 -- 2009; MS064.005.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Friends [2 of 2], 1968 -- 2010; MS064.005.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - General Correspondence [1 of 2], 1975 -- 2010; MS064.005.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - General Correspondence [2 of 2], 1975 -- 1998; MS064.005.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Get Well Cards, MS064.005.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Hawaii Friends, 1969 -- 1998; MS064.005.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Hawaii Students, 1990 -- 2010; MS064.005.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Hsiao, Ruth, 1988 -- 2010; MS064.005.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Richard Hugher, 1972 -- 1993; MS064.005.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Jen, Gish, 1991 -- 1996; MS064.005.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Letters 1980-82, 1980 -- 1982; MS064.005.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Letters - Friends/Adults, 1962 -- 2001; MS064.005.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Miller, Bill, 1994 -- 1998; MS064.005.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Motherwell, Lise, 1990 -- 1994; MS064.005.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Julius Paul Writings, 1959 -- 1962; MS064.005.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Pechet, 1990 -- 2006; MS064.005.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Photographs and poetry, 1990 -- 1991; MS064.005.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Photographs removed from scrapbook, pages 1-8, 1935 -- 1987; MS064.005.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Photographs removed from scrapbook, pages 9-15 and loose photos, 1971 -- 1996; MS064.005.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Photographs from "Food News", 1966; MS064.005.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Pike, Connie, 1984 -- 2008; MS064.005.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Poepoe, Abe, 1989; MS064.005.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Pre-Tufts [Transcript and memo], 1949 -- 1951; MS064.005.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Rasmussen Autobiography, 2007; MS064.005.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Rasmussen, Howard, 2000 -- 2008; MS064.005.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Reintjes, John - Hawaii friend [grsch], 1978 -- 1988; MS064.005.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Resumes, 2004; MS064.005.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Suki Rogers, 1960 -- 2007; MS064.005.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Allan Saunders [1 of 2], 1970 -- 1999; MS064.005.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Allan Saunders [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1999; MS064.005.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Allan & Marion Saunders, 1960 -- 1983; MS064.005.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Stephanie Schlant, 1981 -- 2007; MS064.005.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Cal & Tippy Schwabe (Hawaii friends - grad school), 1976 -- 2008; MS064.005.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Simmons, Adele, 1977 -- 1988; MS064.005.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - Steindler, Jim, 1989; MS064.005.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - Townsley, Sid, 2005 -- 2011; MS064.005.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - Watanabe, Sally, 1992; MS064.005.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - Webb, Robert and Betty, 1972 -- 2007; MS064.005.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - Westminster West Farm, 1984 -- 1985; MS064.005.005.00045 (Box 5)
  - Woffords, 1962 -- 2002; MS064.005.005.00046 (Box 5)
  - Harris Wofford's Articles, 1960 -- 1977; MS064.005.005.00047 (Box 5)
  - Yamamoto, Margy - Secretary for the JACL, Washington, 2003 -- 2005; MS064.005.005.00048 (Box 5)
  - Yee, Alfred, 1973 -- 1975; MS064.005.005.00049 (Box 5)
  - Cooking Class Photographs, 1971 -- 1976; MS064.005.005.00050 (Box 5)